<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Career on Ong Aun Ter</title>
    <link>https://ongaunter.netlify.app/categories/career/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Career on Ong Aun Ter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ongaunter.netlify.app/categories/career/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Assisted Learning and Support</title>
      <link>https://ongaunter.netlify.app/post/02_career/assisted_learning_and_support/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ongaunter.netlify.app/post/02_career/assisted_learning_and_support/</guid>
      <description>The Role of Experienced Individuals in Assisted Learning Experienced individuals play a crucial role in assisted learning, leveraging their accumulated knowledge to guide learners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build Your Professional Brand</title>
      <link>https://ongaunter.netlify.app/post/02_career/build_your_professional_brand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ongaunter.netlify.app/post/02_career/build_your_professional_brand/</guid>
      <description>Understanding Professional Branding Professional branding is the process of presenting yourself to others as an expert in your industry. This can be done by showcasing your skills, experiences, and personal attributes in a way that positions you as a leader in your field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Career Development</title>
      <link>https://ongaunter.netlify.app/post/02_career/career_development/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ongaunter.netlify.app/post/02_career/career_development/</guid>
      <description>Understanding Career Development Career development is a lifelong process of managing learning, work, and transitions to move toward a personally determined and evolving preferred future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skills vs. Degrees: Which Matters More in the Tech Industry?</title>
      <link>https://ongaunter.netlify.app/post/02_career/skills_vs_degree/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ongaunter.netlify.app/post/02_career/skills_vs_degree/</guid>
      <description>Valuing Degrees in the Tech Industry In the tech industry, formal degrees have long been seen as a testament to one&amp;rsquo;s knowledge and expertise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Industry Burnout: Why Your Dream Job Might Turn into a Nightmare</title>
      <link>https://ongaunter.netlify.app/post/02_career/tech_career_burnout/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ongaunter.netlify.app/post/02_career/tech_career_burnout/</guid>
      <description>The Demanding Pace of the Tech Industry The tech industry is renowned for its rapid pace and constant innovation. While this can be exciting, it also means that employees often have to deal with tight deadlines, high workloads, and the continuous pressure to learn new technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hard Truths You Need to Know Before Making the Leap into Tech</title>
      <link>https://ongaunter.netlify.app/post/02_career/truths_of_leaping_into_tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ongaunter.netlify.app/post/02_career/truths_of_leaping_into_tech/</guid>
      <description>The Unavoidable Learning Curve Embarking on a journey into the tech industry involves confronting a steep learning curve. Regardless of your background, the tech industry demands constant learning and adaptation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Perfect Fit Fallacy</title>
      <link>https://ongaunter.netlify.app/post/02_career/perfect_fit_fallacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ongaunter.netlify.app/post/02_career/perfect_fit_fallacy/</guid>
      <description>Addressing the Myth of the Perfect Fit For countless years, many people have pursued the idea of a &amp;ldquo;perfect fit&amp;rdquo; career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Pros and Cons of Switching to a Tech Career Mid-Life</title>
      <link>https://ongaunter.netlify.app/post/02_career/switching_into_tech_midlife/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ongaunter.netlify.app/post/02_career/switching_into_tech_midlife/</guid>
      <description>Pros of Switching to a Tech Career Mid-Life Switching to a tech career mid-life can bring several advantages. First, the tech industry is renowned for its high earning potential and abundance of job opportunities, which can provide a significant career boost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Switching to a Career in Tech Might Be a Huge Mistake for Some People</title>
      <link>https://ongaunter.netlify.app/post/02_career/tech_career_switch_mistake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ongaunter.netlify.app/post/02_career/tech_career_switch_mistake/</guid>
      <description>Unrealistic Expectations Switching to a career in tech may seem promising due to high earning potential and flexible work environments. However, for some people, it could be a mistake if expectations are unrealistic.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
